

Arman Ajabkhani SENIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER - JAVA

PROFILE

Gender: Male

Nationality: Iranian **Birth Date**: 8/25/1983

Software engineer with a strong background in design and development on Java platform. Keen learner and problem solver with a passion for algorithms, architecture. Highly experienced in developing financial, payment and banking systems.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science from Sheikh Bahaee Isfahan University in Software Engineering from September 2000 to September 2006.

LANGUAGES

English

Persian

CONTACT

Email: arm.khani@gmail.com

Mobile: +98 912 8589 456

LinkedIn: Arman Ajabkhani's profile Address: No. 23, Parastoo2 Alley, Kaj

St., Taherkhani St., Tehran, Iran

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sava Arman Kish (Bitex)

Senior Java Developer

Nov 2018 - Present

- I currently work as senior java developer of the exchange project.
- I developed reactive java using RxJava and Vert.x and Swagger.
- I design and implement feature in user-account and notification.
- I work in full micro-services architecture.

TOSAN (Payment and Banking solution provider)

Team Tech Lead

Mar 2017 - Nov 2018

- Mentoring, coaching, training and planning tasks for the team members.
- Analysis, Design, Development, Deployment and Maintenance CM team applications.
- Designing and developing some complicated features in open banking API.

TOSAN (Payment and Banking solution provider)

Junior / Senior Java Developer

Nov 2011 - Mar 2017

- I worked as a member of the Channel Manger(CM) team.
- I developed functionalities for tracking and authentication and authorization.
- I developed and implemented Web Services with JAX-WS.
- I implemented many feature in Persistence layer using Hibernate
- I had Extensive experience using framework APIs like spring and Hibernate.

Elm o Sanat

Senior C#/ASP.NET Developer

Sep 2010 – Oct 2011

- I implement several new features in the School product.
- I used Entity Framework in school product and custom report generator.
- I implement virtual replication on SQL Server with use web service.

Netbina (Online Advertising)

Junior C#/ASP.NET Developer

October 2006 - March 2009

- I implemented several functionalities for the advertising products.
- I work on developing a Blog Service with C# and ASP.NET.



Arman Ajabkhani SENIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER - JAVA

PROGRAMMING SKILLS

Core Java 8	Spring
Design Patterns	Spring Boot
SOA	Spring MVC / AOP
Microservices	Spring Batch
Event Driven Architecture	Spring Security
Software Architecture Patterns	Spring Data / JPA
Apache Tomcat	Hibernate
Live Migration	Spring AOP / aspectj
Concurrent Programming	Vert.x
Reactive Programming	Redis / Hazelcast
RESTful Web Services	Oracle PL/SQL Development
SOAP / JAX-WS /JAX-RS	Gradle / Maven
Docker and Docker Compose	Git / Subversion / TFS
CI / CD	Jira / TFS / HP ALM
Jenkins /	Test Driven Development
Swagger	JUnit / TestNg/Power Mock / Mockito
Apache Kafka / ActiveMQ	UML / Agile and RUP Methodologies
OAuth / JWT	CORE Banking / Payment Systems
HTML / CSS / javascript	Confluence / SharePoint / Documenting
C# 4.5/ ASP.NET	Crypto Currency Exchanges
Entity Framework/ WCF	Block Chain / Hyperledger Fabric